Help!
I never should have
trusted that bitch.
Dad!
Zhu Yihai!
I really wish I could live my life over.
I want to live my life over too.
Help! Somebody help!
Bro Hai!
What's wrong with you?
Save who?
Save Zhu Yihai!
Bro, you are Zhu Yihai.
I'm Zhu Yihai?
Yeah.
Boss Lady, what's wrong with him?
Don't tell me he's lost his memory.
What year is it?
1997.
I time-traveled.
Dahai.
Anyway, you're awake now.
Let's go home.
Go back? Go back where?
Back to the pool hall.
Pool hall?
I really did become Zhu Yihai.
Zhu Yihai!
Boss Lady!
You're not dead yet!
Another Boss Lady?
Hey, Dali, what are you yelling about?
Qian Huilian, what are you doing here again?
What?
Do I need to report to you to see Dahai?
This old man has two girlfriends?
Boss Lady, Boss Lady, Boss Lady!
I love eating bananas.
Who did I ever piss off?
Since you two already broke up,
stay away from Dahai from now on.
Dahai.
Don't forget our promise.
Dahai!
What promise do you two have?
We don't have any promises.
I just...
What the heck is vibrating?
What is this?
It's a cell phone, obviously.
A cell phone?
This cell phone...
Brother Yihai!
Are you alright?
Boss Long, you're here.
Thanks to Brother Yihai stepping in,
otherwise I, Long Xiao,
might've lost my life.
I'm not the type to forget a favor.
From now on, Brother Yihai
is Giant Wood Group's Second-in-command.
Greetings, Second-in-command!
Brother Yihai,
here, you're second to one,
above all others.
My Giant Wood Group
will always be half yours, Brother Yihai.
He has that kind of status too?
Let's go, brother.
Big bro's throwing you a welcome dinner.
I actually time-traveled back to 1997,
back when my dad was young.
Today is November 10th, 1997.
Now for today's midday news.
Capital cultural figures held a forum on
the spirit of the 15th National Congress
to foster and flourish our culture.
November 1997.
Damn.
The old man was jailed on Jan 1, 1998.
That's only a month or so away!
This must be a dream.
Brother Yihai.
Get up and party with us!
I can't go to prison.
Bro Hai, what are you talking about?
Quick, knock on wood!
With me, Long Xiao, around,
how could I ever let you go to prison?
Right?
Right, with Boss Long looking out for us,
there's no way you're going to prison.
Here, Boss Long,
let me toast you on Bro Hai's behalf.
Who exactly sent the old man to prison?
Brother Yihai, join in!
Come on!
Come on, today's such a happy day!
Bottoms up!
Hold on.
Come on, come on.
Hey, cut the music for a sec.
Everyone, gather around.
Come on, Brother Yihai,
get over here.
Go on!
Hurry up, get over here.
Today,
I'm handing over all of Aimin Street
to my brother.
Yes!
All right, music back on.
Let's keep drinking.
I object.
Xie Fan.
What are you doing here?
Putting on a show?
I remember now.
The day my dad got out of prison,
he's the one who kidnapped me and my dad.
Xie Fan.
You pulled a knife in the Night City fight.
You broke the rules.
Rules?
You made me hide out for over 20 years,
and now you're lecturing me about rules?
Don't you want to know
how your son has lived all these years?
Come on, take a look.
He's a dog at my Foot Massage Parlor now.
You don't deserve to be my father.
Putting on a show?
Chaoyang.
Bro.
Didn't you promise Aimin Street to me?
Dongxing Factory just got demolished.
You won't just use and discard me, right?
Listen, Xie Fan,
aren't you being a bit too hasty?
Of course I'm hasty.
Because that belongs to me.
Now you're giving it to this scumbag.
How can I not be hasty?
So what if you're hasty? What can you do?
Today is Bro Hai's Victory Banquet.
What you're doing makes it
really tough for Bro Hai.
Tough, huh?
If it's tough, then forget it.
Xie Fan,
you've gone too far.
And you, what are you tagging along for?
Starting a rebellion?
Don't celebrate too soon.
Come on, Brother Yihai.
Old hatreds and new grudges.
Hurry, don't mind them.
These bastards.
I'll discipline him when we get back.
Don't let it ruin our mood today.
Come on, keep drinking.
Come on, keep singing.
Keep eating.
It's all on me, come on, keep going.
Let's keep going, keep going.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Here, Boss Long.
Drink up.
Bottoms up.
Zhu Yihai,
you served 26 years in prison,
and I was an orphan for 26 years.
And now you're living it up.
I hate you,
Zhu Yihai.
Zhu Yihai
So this is where you live?
I thought you were some big shot.
So this is what you look like.
You really deserve a beating.
How could I have become you?
How did I become you?
How did I end up as you?
What did I do to deserve this?
The only sin I ever committed was...
having you as my father.
Do you know on New Year's Day, 1998,
you got locked up for over twenty years?
After you went to prison, my mom died.
I don't even know her name.
I grew up in an orphanage.
Everyone who saw me
would kick me around.
Kick me around.
Your good friend Xie Fan
bullied me
for over twenty years straight.
Do you know what twenty years feels like?
All because of you,
I never felt any love growing up.
Because I had no love at all.
And now I've even become you.
I have to serve your twenty-year sentence.
What am I doing this for?
You'll commit the crime in a month, right?
If I don't commit the crime this month,
I won't have to go to prison, right?
And maybe I can finally meet my mom?
Zhu Yihai,
I'll show you
what a real father looks like.